Hello friends, welcome to
another video of IndiaTech. Friends, today we will
tell you how we
can stop the auto debit facility of our credit card.
So suppose you don't want to pay your bill,
some of your transactions are in dispute
and you don't want
your minimum balance to be
auto-debited from your account on a specific date of the month, you
want to stop it. So today we will
learn how to stop it. So let's start.
For this, first of all,
log in to your internet banking. So, see, I
logged in by entering my user ID and password. So,
when you log in, you will
go to this section, Cards and Loans.
After that, you will go to the section, Cards and Loans. After that, you will click on Credit Card.
When you click on it,
your credit card number and
its details will appear here. After that, you have to
go to the left here and see, you have an
option called Auto Debit Setup. Click on it.
When you click on Auto Debit Setup, you will
see it. If you have
multiple cards, then you
can select your card from the drop down.
Now, this no.  If you mark it as yes
and see this is your account number, if
you mark it as yes and submit it, then your
minimum amount will be
automatically debited on every billing cycle, if you
want you can also make it the total amount,
so the total amount will be
automatically debited from your account on the billing cycle,
but if we want to mark it as no, then mark it as no
and leave it as anything, it does
not make any difference because we have marked the setup for
debit, and after that you
submit it, then
see this auto debit
instruction confirmation will come, if you want to mark it as no, then
see a message will come, your
request has been successfully submitted, so
now there will be no auto debit on your billing cycle,
nor the minimum amount, so you have to keep in
mind that when your cycle is getting completed
and when it is the last date for submitting your billing cycle, then
you will have to
go and pay the bill manually, otherwise
your charges will be levied, so this was today's
video, if you liked this video then
you can like it.  Please share
and thank you so much for watching.